medicalcodingdegrees.net 2015-12-06

# MEDICALCODINGDEGREES.NET

MEDICALCODINGDEGREES.NET understands that you are concerned about how your information is used and shared. This notice explains our privacy policy and how your information may or may not be used by our site.

BY VISITING MEDICALCODINGDEGREES.NET YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE TERMS DESCRIBED IN OUR PRIVACY POLICY. PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY SO THAT YOU UNDERSTAND OUR ONLINE PRIVACY PRACTICES REGARDING:

  * Information we collect
  * How we use the information
  * How we share your information, if at all
  * Your choices

We may make available shorter versions of this Privacy Policy. We also may supplement this policy for specific Services. Where there is a conflict between this policy and our summary this policy will govern. Where there is a conflict between this policy and our supplement, the supplement will govern.

We may change this privacy policy. If we change this policy we will post the changes to this privacy statement, our websites' homepages, and other places we deem appropriate. We reserve the right to modify this policy at any time. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

## What Personally Identifiable Information (PII) does MEDICALCODINGDEGREES.NET gather?

Information we gather on our site helps us enhance the experience that future visitors may have on our site. Here are the types of information we gather:

## Information You Give Us

We collect information from you when you use our site, navigate around our site, register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to survey, or fill out a form.

On our site, you will find a variety of forms. Each form pertains to a particular school or educational institution. Each form may collect Personally Identifiable Information (PII) such as name, phone number, email address, postal address, gender, and age. Not all forms require all the information. You can choose not to provide the information, but you may not be able to complete the process of requesting information from that school. We use the information you provide to inform the schools of your interest and the best way of getting in contact with you. You may be contacted via phone, text, postal mail, or email by a representative of the school. You may request information from more than one school, which means you may be contacted by each school. We may sell your information to other partner companies if your request for information is rejected by a school. In this case a partner may contact you with other educational offers. If you opt into the newsletter, you may receive other info from our site or our partners. This is not a required question to complete the form.

We also want you to know that we do at times send the information to third party validation services to ensure all of the information is accurate and true. This helps us ensure that the schools which you are requesting information from have the most accurate way of getting in contact with you.

## Automatic Information

We receive and store certain types of information when you interact with our site. Our site uses cookies like many other sites. This helps us determine what browser you are using and how to best present the information to you. Some automatic information examples are: browser type, operating system, IP address, and date and time of information request. You can disable cookies in your web browser, however this may affect the experience you have on our site, since you may not be able to see all of the features. The cookies we set do have an expiration date and will automatically be disabled after the expiration date.

## Information From Other Sources

We do receive information from other sources and append this to the information that is sent to each school. Examples of this information are the following: source of where you initially clicked on an advertisement, what ad you clicked on, what you may have typed into a search engine, etc. This information helps us better optimize your user experience based on your information needs.

## Does MEDICALCODINGDEGREES.NET share the information we receive?

Information about our customers is very important to us. We do reserve the right to sell the information to other parties. If you wish to be removed from being contacted by our partners, simply email us at [contactus@MEDICALCODINGDEGREES.NET](mailto:contactus@MEDICALCODINGDEGREES.NET).

We also use this information to provide targeted advertisements.

Our relationships and contracts with the schools prohibit us from contacting you directly without your expressed consent.

## What type of Information might I receive from MEDICALCODINGDEGREES.NET?

If you do opt-in to our newsletter, we may on occasion send out information that we deem of interest to you. This could range from helpful hints about education to other advertising offers such as but not limited to loan offers, and/or consumer product offers.

If you wish to opt out of our newsletter, you can unsubscribe at any time by going to the following link: Unsubscribe Me

## What information can I access?

MEDICALCODINGDEGREES.NET believes in transparency and accessibility. If you wish to delete your information from our database, please send a written request to [contactus@MEDICALCODINGDEGREES.NET](mailto:contactus@MEDICALCODINGDEGREES.NET). Your request will be processed within 10 business days.

If you wish to remove your contact information from a particular school, you must contact that school directly. You can also email us, and we will forward on your request to the appropriate representatives at each school. It usually takes about 10 days for all parties to comply with your request.

## How safe is my information?

At MEDICALCODINGDEGREES.NET we currently do not collect information such as social security numbers or credit card numbers. If we do in the future change this policy, we will ensure that this information is transmitted in a secure environment. At the moment, we only collect information that is publicly accessible and can often be found in phone books or internet search engines. Therefore, we currently do not offer SSL encryption on our site.

## If I have a problem with my data, how can I resolve it?

We are committed to helping you resolve your dilemma as quickly as possible. Please contact us through email at [contactus@MEDICALCODINGDEGREES.NET](mailto:contactus@MEDICALCODINGDEGREES.NET). This email box is checked during business working days only. We are committed to resolving any issues in a timely manner.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that sites and service providers may transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser. They enable the site and service provider systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. You can turn off cookies in your settings at any time.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

We may use Cookies to provide a targeted advertising experience on and off our site.

## Multi-site Advertising

We have online Behavorial Advertising on our Site.

Advertisers and advertising networks use tracking technologies to collect information about users' computers or mobile devices and their online activities (for example, web pages visited and searches made) as well as general geographic location and use that information to display targeted ads to users. We sometimes allow these ad companies to collect such information when you use our sites and apps to enable them to display targeted ads to you on and off our Site.

Many ad companies are members of the Network Advertising Initiative. NAI members allow users to opt out of being tracked by cookies. To opt out of cookie tracking by NAI members, you may visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/> and click on the "Consumer Opt-out" button. Companies may also be members of the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA") and to opt out of cookie tracking by DAA members, you may visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>.

## Conditions of Use

By using and accessing MEDICALCODINGDEGREES.NET you are agreeing to the Online Privacy Policy set forth. As our business changes and grows, we may change the privacy policy. Any changes will be posted on our site. Please check back often for any updates.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account via the "Sign In" link on the top right of the home page. Then click on 'Page Settings' and then go to the 'Account' section.

## Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

## Contact Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may [Contact Us](mailto:contactus@MEDICALCODINGDEGREES.NET) at:

**MEDICALCODINGDEGREES.NET**  
588 Sutter St. #551  
San Francisco, CA 94102  
contactus@MEDICALCODINGDEGREES.NET 

Last Updated: March 4, 2014.
